小时候 黑夜总是可怕的
When you're little Nighttime is scary
因为总觉得床下藏着鬼怪
Because there are monsters Hiding right under the bed.
长大了
When you get older
鬼怪也跟着变了
The monsters are different...
变作了自我怀疑
Self-doubt...
孤独寂寞
Loneliness...
遗憾悔恨
Regret.
即使我们长大了 聪明了
And though you may be older And wiser
我们依旧害怕黑夜
You still find yourself Scared of the dark.
我疯了 就是这样 发疯了
I'm crazy. That's what.This is--craziness.
-你没发疯 -那这是怎么回事?
-You're not crazy. -Then what is this?
你 你 你 你是什么
What--what--what-- What are you?
-我是个深爱着你的已故之人 -这是我的幻想
-I'm a dead man who loves you. -This is my imagination.
我想象力一向非常丰富
I've always had a very active imagination.
伊兹 你触碰过我
Izzie you touched me.
你还活着的时候 我触碰过你 还亲过你
I touched you when you Were alive and kissed you.
往事不可追
Everything that's happening Has happened.
我只是在重温旧梦 残念作祟
I'm--i'm reliving moments. This is just residual grief.
好吧 我猜唯一的证明方法就是
All right so i guess The only way to test it
做一些
Is to do something
我们之前从没有机会做的事
We never got a chance to do In real life.
杨医生
Dr. Yang?
亨特医生
Dr. Hunt.
你是来找我的吗
Are you here for me?
什么
What?
我是说 我的创伤科
I-i meant my--my trauma.
我来 是因为可能有一个阑尾炎切除
I'm here For a possible appy.
救护车就要到了
The ambulance Is on its way in.
你是想说什么吗
Did you want To say something?
你怎么会比救护车先到
H-how'd you beat The ambulance?
我就住在街对面
I live across the street.
你家的沙发烂透了
Your sofa sucks.
我根本睡不着
I can't sleep.
我今晚就没睡
I never went to bed.
你经常在浴室地板上看书
You usually read On the bathroom floor?
我不想吵醒德里克
I didn't want To wake derek.
这些是我妈妈的日志
These are My mother's journals
从她还是个住院医师开始写起的
From when She was a resident.
-我还以为我们讨厌你妈呢 -我有点觉得
-I thought we hated Your mother. -You know i kinda think now
如果我不是她女儿 我会喜欢她的
If i wasn't her child I would've liked her.
我是说 她很有趣 又很专注
I mean she was funny And intense.
-很像克里斯蒂娜 -克里斯蒂娜确实专注
-A lot like cristina. -Oh yeah."intense" i get from cristina.
但我可不觉得她有趣
"funny " not so much.
她这个人确实很慢热
Oh she takes a while To warm up
可是一旦熟悉了 她就成了克里斯蒂娜
But when she does She's cristina.
给她个机会 她这个人忠贞不二
Give her a chance. She's very loyal
你在医院里需要死党
And we need allies Around here.
你觉得她怎么样 她叫什么来着
What do you think about Uh what's her name
-你妹妹莱西 -我觉得她怎么样
-Your sister lexie? -What do i think about her?
她做我的死党怎么样 新的实习死党
Yeah as an ally for me. My new intern b.f.f.
不 我 不不 我没什么好说的
No i--no no i don't-- I don't see that. I just--
她在正常家庭和教育下长大
She was raised right With parents and rules
脸上洋溢着迷人的微笑
And smiley-face posters On her wall.
是克里斯蒂娜 有个阑尾切除手术
It's cristina. There's an appy.
看 这才是死党
See? Loyalty.
我和你一起去
I'll come with you.
去技术训练室打发打发时间
Try to snag some time In the skills lab.
-我马上穿好衣服 -好的
-I'll get dressed. -Okay.
我的天
Oh! Oh my god.
火爆
Hot.
淫乱
Horny.
你怎么 你怎么站在哪儿
Oh what--what are you Doing out here?
你以为只有你买通护士
You think you're the only one Who paid off a nurse
-一有阑尾切除手术就呼你 -我说的不是这个
-To page you with an appy? -That's not what i meant.
我说的是这个
That's what i meant.
你在这儿 那谁在里面
If you're out here Then who's in there with izzie?
-我的天 -德里克
-Oh my god! -Derek?
怎么了
Oh! What?
怎么了 发生什么了
Oh. What? What's the matter?
没事没事 我只是
Nothing. Nothing. I just um...
-半夜3点你穿戴整齐干什么去 -天啊
-What are you doing dressed? It's 3:00 in the morning.
谁在伊兹的房间看A片
Oh!Who's making a porno movie In izzie's room?
别紧张 她在自慰 可真火爆
Oh relax. She's flying solo. That's hot.
伊兹 派对结束了 有个阑尾切除术
Iz the party's over. We got an appy coming in.
死神 走吧
Death let's go.
她也住这儿 死神
She's living here too Death?
只是找到房子前小住几天
Just for a couple of days Until she gets her own place
-然后她就走 -别再收留人了
-And then she's gone. -No more strays.
不收留了
No more strays.
伊兹 伊兹 出来
Hey iz. Iz come on.
那么
Um so
我 我 我不太舒服
Yeah i'm not--i'm not-- I'm not feeling that great.
我还是不去了 我不知道
I think i'm gonna skip it. I don't know.
-我可能感冒了或者食物中毒 -你汗流浃背
-I think i have the flu or maybeIt's food poisoning. I
我很热 你知道的 感冒
Yeah. Yeah i'm hot...And you know cold.
又热又冷 我都打颤了
Hot and cold. I have the chills.
我还是回去睡觉好了
Yeah i think i'm just Gonna go back to bed.
听起来你不像在睡觉
It didn't sound like You were sleeping.
你知道 我也可以不去留下来照顾你
You know i could skip the appy And help you out if you want.
不不 我可不想传染你
No! No i'm... I don't want To get you sick too so...
你们在这儿干吗
What are you all doing here?
-他是我的 我看到救护车的 -我俩一起
-Oh uh he's mine.I met the ambulance. -And she's sharing him With me.
-我的 我值班 -早上好 贝利医生 你今天真漂亮
-He's mine. I'm on call. -Good morning dr. Bailey. You look nice today.
马屁精 我先来的
Brownnoser. I got here first.
-主任说我是重点培养对象 -我明白了
-And the chief said I'm the one to watch. -Oh i get it.
主刀手术要到了 你们都打听到
It's solo surgery time And you all have heard
前两年都是阑尾切除术
The past two years the chief Has assigned an appendectomy
所以你们这群小家伙半夜爬起来
So you little mini surgeons Dragged your butts out of bed
想从大师我这儿偷点经验
To pick up some final tips From the master.
-精神可嘉 我可以选两个 -是我当班
-Yeah it's kinda cute. All right i can use two of you. -But i'm on call.
-我已经把病情告诉梅瑞狄斯了 -jason kron 47岁
-I-i just filled meredith in On the case. -Jason Kron 47
右下腹处有压痛感
Tenderness Over mcburney's point.
克莱夫 你对科隆先生的病情了解多少?
Huh. Karev what do you know about mr. Kron?
我知道您主刀 真是他几辈子修来的福分
I know he's a lucky man To have you as a surgeon.
亚瑟 斯特诺夫 45岁 从2楼窗户摔下来
Arthur Soltanoff 45 fell from A second story window.
体征稳定
Stable vitals
多处骨折创伤
Multiple fractures And lacerations
-头部有明显外伤 -一号诊室
-With evidence of head trauma. -Trauma one.
-贝利医生 给我个住院医师 -我 我的 我值班
-Dr. Bailey i'm gonna need One of your residents. -Me. Mine. I'm on call.
-是你的了 -贝利医生 有个病人剧烈腹痛
-It's yours. -Dr. Bailey we have a patient With severe abdominal pain.
能派一个住院医生过来吗?
Can you spare a resident?
好的 格蕾和杨 为科隆先生做术前准备
All right grey and yang Prep mr. Kron for surgery.
克莱夫 剧烈的腹痛也可能
Karev you never know.
发展为一场阑尾切除术
Severe abdominal pain Could become an appendectomy.
贝利医生 我随叫随到
Dr. Bailey i'm here to help In any way that i can.
我时刻准备着为病人接触痛苦
If there's a patient in pain I'm there.
有感觉吗 有感觉吗
Can you feel that? Can you feel that?
完全没有必要这样 我有感觉
There's no need for you to be Doing that. I can feel that.
所有的住院医师都在忙
Okay the residents are here. All of them.
他们都在医院里忙 你们在做什么
They're in the hospital So whatever you're doing...
你们在做什么
What are you doing?
我们对他进行了麻醉
We gave him an epidural.
-你们都没叫我 -莱西
-And didn't call me? -Lexie.
-刚做而已 -麻醉不是说做就做的
-It just happened. -You know what?Epidurals don't just happen.
我住在死神家里
I'm staying at death's.
-十分钟我就能赶过来的 -你住梅瑞狄斯家
-I could've been here In ten minutes. -You're staying at meredith's?
-莱西 -怎么了
-Lexie. -What?
兄弟们 他尿床了
Oh dude. He peed himself.
-我们忘记接导尿管了 -别 别接导尿管
-We forgot The catheter. -No no catheters.
-你还想尿床吗 -不
-You want To pee yourself again? -No.
-好吧 -麻醉 真厉害
-It's okay. -An epidural hmm? Wow. I'm impressed.
死神真是看错你了
Death is so wrong about you.
怎么 她说了什么
Why? What did she say?
她说你是个娇娇小姐
That you're a priss.
真可惜他没怀孕 不然我们就可以剖腹产了
Too bad he's not pregnant. We could do a c-section.
-我们可以帮你割阑尾 -或者截肢
-We could take out His appendix. -Or amputate his foot.
我认真的
Seriously.
阑尾反正可有可无
He doesn't need his appendix.
可以找一个空着的手术是 切除他的阑尾
We could take out his appendix. We'll find an empty o.r.
一个小时就能完事
We'll be in and out In an hour.
-我可在这儿躺着呢 -你可以看啊
-I'm sitting right here. -Oh you could watch.
我们都不用帮你麻醉了
We wouldn't even Have to put you under.
-反正已经麻醉过了 -我明天有空
-You'd just stay On the epidural. -I'm off tomorrow.
我可以和他换班 这样他就可以休息了
I'd trade and take his shift So he could recover.
但是医生们都在啊
But they're all here.
他们忙着争抢主刀手术呢
They're busy chasing Solo surgeries.
这主意太有才了 我们会成功的
It's a genius idea. We would be rock stars.
不行 我绝不同意在小鸡鸡上插尿管
No. I draw a line At a tube in my penis.
绝不
Line drawn.
好吧
Fine.
我来
Do me.
从我开始 一个个按顺序来
As long as i can do One of you guys next.
成交
Done.
什么情况
What do we got?
多处创伤 谢博德和亨特正在会诊
Massive injuries. Shepherd And hunt are working on him.
睡觉时梦游 撞穿了窗户
Guy was sleepwalking And took a 2-story header
从2楼跌了下来
Through a plate glass window.
-夜惊 -能想象吗
-Night terrors. -Can you imagine?
一觉醒来 浑身是伤
You wake up you're battered You're bruised
-不知身处哪里从何而来 -就是我的写照嘛
-You don't know where you are Or how you got there. -Yeah That sounds like my life--
结婚 背叛 同性恋 被甩
Married betrayed Gay abandoned
一觉醒来 真不知道我怎么会成了这样
And then i woke up and had No idea how i got here.
这肯定是我人生的低谷
I just figure This is the bottom.
非常低谷 不会更低了
This is as bad as it gets. It can only go up from here.
除了左胫骨和腓骨 其余的外伤都清理好了
Left tib/fib. The rest Of his trauma series is clear.
-他要做CT脑内有积水 天啊 -不要 ivy 离开哪儿
-He needs a head c.t. He's got Free fluid in there. Oh god. -No Ivy Get out of the way!
-爸爸 -依维 前面有只美洲狮
-Dad. -Ivy the mountain lion's Right there.
-先生 你现在在医院 -依维 我女儿呢
-Sir you're in a hospital. -Ivy! Where's my daughter?
-爸爸 我在这 -它要杀我女儿 -他还在睡
-Dad i'm right here! -He's gonna kill my daughter. -He's still asleep.
-放开我 我要救我女儿 -冷静 斯特诺尔先生
-Let me go. I've gotta get My daughter. -Calm down. Mr. Soltanoff Calm down.
-来人帮帮忙 -救依维
-Could we get Some help here please. -Get Ivy!
-斯特诺夫先生 冷静 -依维 她需要我 放开我
-Mr. Soltanoff calm down.Please. -Ivy! She needs me. Let go!
她需要我
Oh she needs me!
放开我 她需要我
Let go! She needs me!
好了 贝利在第二手术室进行阑尾切除
Okay bailey's got an appy in o.r. Two
所以这一层是空的
So this floor is out
不过我们的手术完全开放
But out patient surgery Is totally open.
好的 走吧
Okay let's go.
找什么呢
Looking for something?Hi um uh...
我们带赛迪逛逛
We were giving sadie The tour.
这是手术安排板
Uh this is the o.r. Board. Yeah.
这是病人
And--and--and this is A patient.
你很幸运 格蕾医生非常出色
Um you're in good hands. Dr. Grey is an excellent doctor.
你们等下去哪儿逛
What's next on the tour?
回技术训练室
Back to skills lab?
技术训练室 好主意
Skills lab. Great idea.
要和我的死党走了噢
Gotta stick with my allies.
娇笑的小姑娘 我说过了的
Smiley-face posters. That's all i'm saying.
hammer女士 什么问题
Mrs. Hammer what seems To be the problem?
我胃好痛
Uh i have this pain In my stomach
没办法消化
And i can't keep food down.
食物没经消化就排出了
It just goes Right through me.
告诉他你的结论 lauren 她有结论
Just tell him your theory Lauren. She has a theory.
-我在这儿 我能自己说 -她觉得她得了胃癌
-Okay i'm right here. I can speak. -She thinks She has stomach cancer
因为网上是这么说的
Because the internet Told her so.
没错 我没得妄想症 好吗
Yeah i'm not A hypochondriac okay?
-他又不是我肚子里的蛔虫 -我也有个推论
-He's not inside my body. -I have a theory too -By the way.
-命名就是痢疾 -seth
-It's a crazy disease Called diarrhea. -Seth.
-好吧 我闭嘴 -我么检查下
-Fine. Shutting up. -Let's--let's take a look.
好的
Okay.
你阑尾不痛
You're not tender Over your appendix
所以我们不需要做阑尾切除
So we don't need To take that out.
这很好 不是吗
Well that's a good thing Right?
-你看起来很沮丧 -只是对你很失望
-I mean you look upset. -Mm just disappointed...For you.
我要取下大便样本
I'm gonna have to collect A stool sample.
我真不信会出现这种事
I can't believe This is happening.
反正你的鼻子也不好看
It wasn't A great nose anyway.
不是的 我的鼻子很好看
Yes it was. What-- It was a nice nose.
放松点 我开玩笑呢
Relax. I was kidding.
以前就美呆了
It was a gorgeous nose...Ow.
以后还会这么美
And it will be again.
只要两周
Two weeks from now
-就什么都看不出来了 -真的吗
-You won't even be able To tell anything happened. -Really?
-三周 顶多四周 -我恨你
-m three weeks. Four tops. -I hate you.
你爱我
You love me.Ow.
会有点挤压感
Little pinch.Ow ow ow. Ow. Ow.
拜托 不疼的
Oh come on.That didn't hurt.
如果今年诸事顺利
Yeah well maybe if i was Having a good year
那可能只是挤压感
It would feel likeJust a little pinch.
可是很痛 马克 很痛很痛
But it hurts mark.It hurts a lot. Ow.
知道吗
You know what?
我本来只想局部麻醉
I was gonna do this With some local
但还是全身麻醉吧
But i think we'll use Conscious sedation
这样你一觉醒来 鼻子就已经好了
That way when you wake up Your nose will be fixed
崭新的一天就此开始
And it'll be A whole new day.
至少还有你在我身边 是吗
Okay well at least I'll still have you right?
你还会是我的朋友
You'll still be my friend
需要时和我作爱
And have sex with me When i want?
随叫随到
Anytime.
只要你鼻子修好
You know.Once your face heals.
我恨你
I hate you.
你爱我
You love me.
我打伤了个医生 我不明白
I hit a doctor? I-i don't understand.
-我怎么在这 -你女儿说你做噩梦
-What am i even doing here? -Your daughter said you were
-你跳出了窗户 -你以前梦游吗
-And jumped out of The window. -Do you have a history Of sleepwalking?
几年前我妻子过世时开始的
It started a couple of years ago When my wife died.
我吓坏了 我去过睡眠诊所
It scared me so much i went to One of those sleep clinics.
他们说只是压力过大 给我开了些安定
They said it was stress induced And gave me some clonazepam.
有效吗
How's that been working?
我独自抚养一个13岁的孩子
Well I'm raising a 13 year old
所以工作压力很大
So stress comes with the job.
我有段时间没发作了
I haven't had an episode In a while.
肯定是昨晚忘了吃药
I must have forgotten to take My pill tonight.
亲爱的
Honey...
对不起
I am so sorry.
你肯定吓坏了
You must have been so scared.
我没事 我很好 我只是担心你
I'm okay. I'm fine. I'm just worried about you.
对不起
I'm sorry.
-斯隆医生 -你好
Dr. Sloan. Hi. Hello.
你知不知道静脉注射工具在哪儿
Do you know where they keep The i.v. Kits in here?
实习生们都死哪去了
And where the hell Are all the damn interns?
实习生正在实习
Um the interns Are interning.
忙着实习 非常非常忙
Busily interning.They're v-very busy.
斯隆医生 小格蕾
Dr. Sloan. Little grey.
我来取器械
I needed Some medical supplies.
在器械室碰到了这个实习生
Found the intern In the supply closet.
而不是约她一起来器械室
Did not invite the intern Into the supply closet.
快走 格蕾
Go away now grey.
谢谢
Thank you.
-别这么看我 我什么都没干 -别干
-Stop looking at me like that.I didn't do anything. -Don't do anything.
-我没有 - 别干
-I didn't. -Don't.
我没有
I didn't.
贝利医生 你都不用看腹膜在哪里吗
Dr. Bailey do you have to Visualize the peritoneum?
看情况
Depends.
我做过太多起手术
I've seen so many
我通常靠感觉就行
I can usually just feel it.
你是怎么切割肌肉的 这样还是那样
Did you split the muscle This way or that way?
这样 不 等下
This way. No wait. That--hold up.
那样 习惯成自然 根本不用去多想
That way. It's the kind of thing That becomes so natural You don't even think about it After a while.
你们想太多了
the two of you are thinking so hard
看着你们我都觉得累
You're making me tired Just looking at you.
这很酷
This is so cool.
大伙能相信我们真要做阑尾切割了吗
Can you guys believe We're actually doing this?
麻药应该生效了
The epidural Should be working.
好了 她已经麻醉了
Okay she's numbed.
准备好了
We're ready. Okay.
开始
Here we go.
你没事吗
You okay?
我发现你很有教养
I find the fact that you have parents and rules
招牌式的笑容 让人感觉非常惬意
And smiley-face posters oddly comforting.
什么
What?
我准备好了
I'm ready.
好了 手术标记器 我要标记切口
Okay surgical marker. I'm going to mark the incision.
能拿近点吗
C-c-can you hold that a little bit closer?
好了 上前髂骨脊柱到
Okay One-third of the distance
肚脐的
From the anterior Superior iliac spine
三分之一处
To the umbilicus.
好了
Okay.
大概是这
That's right about...
好了
Okay.
今天是个好日子 让我们来救死扶伤吧
It's a great day To save lives people.
虽然 准确的说你很健康
Although technically your life is just fine and--
晚上到了
It's night time.
-谢博德经常这么说 -就不能直接开始吗
-Oh but shepherd always says that and -Would you just go?
手术刀
Scalpel.
好的
Okay.
这不是个好主意 这主意太糟糕了
This is a bad idea. This is a really bad idea.
现在是半夜
And--and it's the middle Of the night
所以我们脑子都 都 都短路了
So our judgment is you know It--it--it's off.
不过我们可以利用现在的挫败感
But we can use this frustration That--that--that we're feeling
虽然这种挫败感驱使
Th-that's driven us to the point
我们差点做傻事
Where we're about to do a very stupid thing
傻到我们可能在监狱里追悔莫及
A thing that i am certain we'd all regret possibly from jail.
但同时我们也可以将它用在好的地方
And--and we can use The frustration for--for good.
我们可以要求更多的技能培训
We--we can ask for more time In the skills lab
可以要求多进行手术观察
And--and we can ask To observe more surgeries
可以要求住院医师多教教我们
And we can demand that Our residents teach us better.
或者直接取出我的阑尾
Or you could just Take out my appendix.
好的 我在顺着结肠寻找
Okay i'm following The taeniae coli down
阑尾
To expose the appendix.Whoa.
在这儿
There it is.
-看看哪儿 -我也要看
-Look at that. -I want to see.
给她拿个镜子
Get her a mirror.
酷
Ooh. Cool.
怎么了
Huh.What?
你不觉得它有点发炎了吗
Does it look A little inflamed to you?
确实看起来有点发炎
It does... A little. It looks inflamed.
怎么了 书给我看下
What?Can i see the book?
通常 直径应该只有
It's normally Only supposed to be
7到8毫米
7 to 8 millimeters In diameter.
看起来有点大
Yeah. It looks a little big.
如果发炎了 就没有标准程序可言了
If it's inflamed This isn't routine procedure.
这太 我们应该 应该叫个住院医师来
It's a... We should...We should call a resident.
不可以叫住院医师
We're not calling a resident.
对不起 我只是 我真的吓坏了
I'm sorry. I'm just...I'm really freaking out.
听着 我现在是躺在手术台上的人
Listen i'm the one laying open on the table here
我最不想见到你惊慌失措
And the last thing i need is you panicking.
如果你做不到 离开这里
If you can't handle it Leave.
还有其他人吗?
Anybody else?
凯莉夹紧 2号缝线
Kelly clamps and a 2-0 silk.
你爸爸在吗? 我要检查他的缝线
Your dad around? I need to check his stitches.
他还在做检查
He's still having tests.
我待会儿过来
I'll come back.
嘿
Hey.
那个被我爸撞到的医生怎么样了?
How's that doctor my dad hit?
-她没事 -告诉她我真的非常抱歉
-She'll be okay.-Tell her i'm really sorry.
为什么你深感抱歉? 你没有撞倒她
Why are you sorry? You didn't hit her.
是的 只不过...
Yeah. It's just...
如果我当时能让我爸爸睡着...
If i had been able to get my dad back to bed...
有时候我能和他说话直到他入睡
Sometimes i can talk him back to sleep.
但这病已经不止有一段时间了 对吧
But this hasn't happened for a while right
他的梦游病?
Him sleepwalking?
是的
Yeah. Right.
你最后是什么时候睡的?
When's the last time
没事 我不怎么累
It's okay.
说真的 孩子 你应该休息一下
Seriously kid.
你自己诊断自己的病?
So you diagnosed yourself?
-我在网上订购了抗生素防止葡萄状球菌的感染 -我的天啊!
I ordered antibiotics online to kill a staph infection. my god!
我的丈夫认为这只是一个小脓疱
That my husband dismissed as a pimple.
和你的皮肤病医生一起讨论的
Along with your dermatologist.
谁喜欢光看那个 对吧?
Who like barely looked at it okay?
那的确是葡萄状球菌的感染 塞斯 那曾经是 之后就好了
It was a staph infection seth.It was. And it went away.
在我服用了药之后就好了
After i took the drugs it went away.
-小脓疱没有了 -但是你现在检测出有艰难梭菌
Pimples go away. Well now you have c-diff
小脓疱不会自己消退
And it's not going away on its own.
-那我改怎么办? -你已经基本上杀死了
Well how do i treat it? you've basically killed
你身上所有的有益菌
All the healthy bacteria in your body.
-所以我们现在必须引入新的有益菌 -好吧
-So now we have to introduce new healthy bacteria.-Okay.
通过进行
By performing
一个排泄物的移植
What's called a... A-a fecal transplant.
粪便?
Poop?
我要做粪便移植?
I need a poop transplant?
我们要在你的鼻子上培养一小试管的菌
Well we'd feed a small tube up your nose
然后植入你的胃里
And down into your stomach.
捐赠者的条件是
The donor needs to be
一个每天能和你接触到细菌的人
Someone who you share everyday germs with
通常是一对夫妻
Typically a spouse.
承认那是小脓疱
Admit it was a pimple.
-塞斯 -不 我不会在一个碗里排泄
Seth. No i'm not going to crap into a bowl
-直到你承认那是小脓疱 -塞斯
-Until you admit it was a pimple. -Seth.
就这样说定了 你准备好了过来找我
That's the deal. When you're ready come and find me.
就告诉他那是小脓疱吧
Come on. Just tell him it was a pimple.
那不是一个小脓疱
It was not a pimple.
我的实习医生没有一个回复我的呼机
None of my interns are answering their pages.
他们都回家了还是他们只是不--
Did they go home or did they just not--
喂 叫你呢 其他小屁孩呢?
Hey you. Where are the other morons?
我不知道 我只是拿点糖果
I don't know.I was just getting candy.
我不知道
I don't know.
显然
Clearly.
我不知道 我什么都不知道
I don't know. I don't know anything.
嘿
Hey.
给我你的巧克力
Give me your chocolate.
不 所有的 那个也给我
No all of it.No give me that too.
实习生都去哪儿?
Where are the stooges?
刚刚那个小屁孩就是
Well that moron is a moron
其他的也都是擅离职守的
And the other morons are a.w.o.l.
我需要一个实习生在我的病人同意排泄呼我
I need an intern to page me if my guy agrees to crap.
我想他们是不是在技能实验室里
I wonder if they're in the skills lab.
-赛迪说过有关技能实验室的事 -赛迪在医院里?
-Sadie said something about skills lab.-Sadie's in the hospital?
一直待在技能实验室里事实上就是等着被解雇
All that time in the skills lab is actually paying off.
我的实习生还是傻帽
My interns are still idiots
但至少这些傻帽能进入名牌大学
But at least they're idiots that can put in an i.v.
不 他们只是傻帽
No they're just idiots.
伊兹怎么了?
So... What's going on with izzie?
我不知道伊兹怎么了
I don't know what's wrong with izzie.
我讨厌不跟别人说事的人
I'm sick of people not talking to each other.
我要帮我那个病人去排泄
I'm gonna go get my crap chick some crap.
梅瑞狄斯
Meredith.
你有空吗?
Do you have a sec?
2号 你知道你在干什么吗?
Two what do you think you're doing?
制作图表 我只是在制作图表
Charting. I'm only charting.
3号4号还有2号在哪儿?
Where's--where's 3 and 4.2?
我不知道 我想他们--
I-i don't know. I thought they were--
你知道吗? 不要说了 跟我来
You know what? Stop talking. Come with me.
你要做一个阑尾的术后恢复工作
You're gonna do the post-op orders on the appy
然后你要告诉我所有的任何困难
And you're gonna tell me all about whatever trouble
你和你的小朋友们也要参加
You and your little friends are into.
你要我用皮带系住你吗? 我们走吧
Do you need a leash? Let's go.
不
No.
你什么意思 不去?
What do you mean no?
我的意思是...
I mean...
我有点不能走路...
I k-kind of can't walk...
因为导尿管还连着
Due to the catheter and the epidural.
我能听见你的心脏在跳动...
I can hear your heart beating...
这很奇怪
Which is odd
因为他们曾经在验尸解剖中取出你的心脏
Because they took it out for the autopsy.
这个不是真的 对吗?
This isn't real is it?
这是真的
This is real.
伊兹 这是真的
Izzie this is real.
我只是想一直闭着眼睛
I'm just gonna keep my eyes closed
因为这就像早晨的那一刻
Because this is like that moment in the morning
当你刚醒来的时候 你还处于半醒半睡的状态
When you first wake up and you're still half asleep
一切都似乎是..
And everything seems...
都有可能发生 梦境感同身触
Things are possible.Dreams feel true
在睡着和醒来间的那一刻
And for that one moment between waking and sleeping
这些都是真的
Anything can be real.
然后你睁开眼睛 然后太阳照到你 接着...
And then you open your eyes and the sun hits you and...
你意识到...
And you realize that...
我只是想一直闭着眼睛
I'm just gonna keep my eyes closed.
好吧
Okay.
我想她快要死了
I think she's dying.
-她的血压骤降
Her b.p. Is dangerously low.
-我们需要注射2升的试剂 -我们要呼叫紧急治疗吗?
-We need to push 2 liters of l.r.-Should we call a code?
门诊病人的手术中没有紧急治疗小组
There is no code team in outpatient surgery
因为通常 在半夜里
In the middle of the night because normally
这些步骤都由一个外科医生在正规的手术室里完成
This procedure would be done by a surgeon in a regular o.r.
呼叫主任 叫贝利医生来
Page the chief and go get bailey
告诉她这里有紧急情况
And tell her
你不要再废话 把受惊的表情
You're not to say anything else and take that crazy look
给我收起来
Off your face.
嘿 索特诺夫先生怎么样了?
Hey how's mr. Soltanoff?
我觉得他晚上受到的惊吓发生的比他知道的还要多
I think his night terrors are
那个孩子已经筋疲力尽了
The kid's exhausted.
晚上入睡会很可怕
It's gotta be scary going to bed at night
-不知道醒来会是怎么样的 -听上去好像和梅瑞狄斯住一起一样
Not knowing what you're gonna wake up to.Sounds like living with meredith.
她把小格蕾带进来
She takes in strays.
这是你的不对
It's your fault you know.
我从来没对小格蕾有歪念
I never thought about little grey in that way
直到你告诉我不要
Until you told me not to.
现在我无能为力 你撒下的种子
Now i can't help it.You planted a seed.
给我铲掉
Unplant it.
她想和你说些事
She wants to tell you something.
我相信你认为那是一个小脓疱
I believe that you believe it was a pimple.
劳伦
Lauren.
我只能做到这步了
That's the best i can do.
我相信你认为那是
I believe that you believe it was--
那是一个小脓疱
It was a pimple.
那是葡萄状球菌的感染
It was a staph infection.
没有排泄物 没有排泄物给你
No poo. No poo for you.
等一下 伙计 她可以对你撒谎
All right wait dude.She could lie to you
然后告诉你你想听到的 但是她没有
And tell you what you want to hear but she's not.
她在告诉你她真实的情况
She's telling you what's real for her.
不要走开
Stop walking away.
我还是认为这可能是胃癌
I still think this could be stomach cancer.
当我头疼的时候 我觉得是脑瘤
And when i get a headache I think it's a brain tumor.
然后我躺着 然后我感到胸口有肿块
And i lay awake and feel lumps in my breasts
然后我的心脏加速跳动
And then my heart starts to race
然后我觉得我有心脏病
And i think I'm having a heart attack.
所以 不是的 我觉得不是一个小脓疱
So no i don't think it was a pimple.
这个世界是一个恐怖的地方
The world is a scary place...
每天都有数以千计的事情发生
And there are a thousand things a day
它们会将你置于死地
That can kill you.
我不明白为什么你不明白
And i don't see how you don't see it.
贝利医生
Dr. Bailey...
门诊手术室有个紧急情况
There's an emergency in outpatient surgery.
怎么样的紧急情况?
What kind of emergency?
就是一个紧急情况
There's a...It's an emergency.
请过来一下
Please come.
我想做一个脑电图 有可能
I'd like to do an e.e.g.There's a chance
你晚上受到的惊吓是大脑前页引起的
That your night terrors are caused by a kind of epilepsy
-癫痫导致的 -在睡眠诊所里我都做过
-In the frontal lobe of your brain. -I-i went through all that in the sleep clinic.
只要我吃药就没事了
As long as i take my meds--
我们有理由相信那个问题
We have reason to believe that the problem
-可能会比你意识到的更糟糕 -我不明白
May be a lot worse than you're aware of. I don't understand.
艾维 你爸爸多久梦游一次?
Ivy how often does your dad sleepwalk?
我有睡觉的 这次只是忘了吃药而已
I sleep. I just forgot my meds this time.
不 你不是的
No you didn't.
我刷牙的时候你也在梦游
You took them while i was brushing my teeth
你一直都这样 然后把我放到床上
Like you always do and then you put me to bed
你一直都这样
Like you always do
然后醒来尖叫 你一直都这样
And then you woke up screaming like you always do.
-艾维 -我尽量晚上都不睡着
-Ivy -I try to stay awake at night
因为通常我能和你说话使你入睡
Because usually I can talk you back to bed.
但是今天晚上 我肯定是睡着了
But tonight I must have fallen asleep.
宝贝 你为什么不早告诉我?
Honey Why didn't you tell me?
你说过噩梦都是由压力引起的
You said these bad dreams were caused by stress
-我是你的压力 -亲爱的
-And i'm your stress. -Sweetheart
-你白天把我照顾得很好
You take such good care of me during the day
我想我起码能够做的
I thought the least i could do
是在晚上照顾好你 爸爸
Was take care of you at night dad.
但我们所说的噩梦是由癫痫所引起的
But we're saying the nightmares were caused by the epilepsy
不是压力
Not the stress.
如果检查确认是癫痫
And if the test confirms the epilepsy
你知道 那将意味着什么吗?
You understand what that would mean?
这不是我的错?
This wasn't my fault?
那不是你的错
That it wasn't your fault.
爸爸...
Dad...
我们做电脑图吧
Let's get the e.e.g.
亲爱的
Sweetheart.
丹尼?
Denny?
-丹尼?天啊 -你叫什么?
-Denny? God. -What's all the yelling about?
你不能这么做 你不能就这样消失
You can't do that. You can't just disappear.
-我还以为你走了呢 -我只不过
-I thought you were gone. -I was just
我以为你又再一次离开我了
I thought you had left me again.
-伊兹 我告诉过你 我一直为你而在这里 -不 你没有
Izzie i told you I'm here for you. No you're not.
你死了 你死了 然后你在这里离开我了
You died. You died and you left me here.
我一个人留在这里 你离开我了 只剩我一个人孤零零的
I was left here by myself.You left me... All alone.
你不会再孤单了
You're not alone anymore.
为什么? 为什么你要回来?
Why?Why did you come back?
我已经恢复过来了 我忘记你了
I had moved on.I-i got over you.
我有了新的生活 工作 男朋友
I have a life and a job and a boyfriend
但是 你回来了 我在这间房间里呆了一天
And--and now you're back and i'm in this room all day
或许是在和我自己说话
Probably talking to myself.
我可能要疯了
I'm probably going crazy
房间外面有一个真实的世界
And there is a real world out there
我却在这里被你哄骗
And i'm stuck in here with you.
我很抱歉我曾经死了
I'm sorry i died.
不 不 去死吧
No. No screw you.
不 你不必为死亡道歉
No you don't get to apologize for dying.
-你不必为死亡道歉 因为我是我杀了你! -伊兹
You don't get to apologize Because i killed you! Izzie
我说服你让我切除导管
I convinced you to let me cut the l-vad
是我杀了你
And i killed you
-所以你不必为死亡道歉 -伊兹
So you don't get to apologize for dying. -Izzie
-死亡的人不会道歉 -伊兹
Dead people don't apologize. -Izzie
不 闭嘴
No just shut up.
闭嘴
Shut up.
我爱你
I love you.
我也爱你
I love you too.
到底怎么了?
What the hell is going on?
我们刚才正准备拿出她的阑尾
We were trying to take out her appendix.
-谁的笨主意? -我的
-Well whose foolish idea was that? -Mine.
什么进度了?
Where are we?
我们刚刚找到阑尾系膜的动脉
We just found the artery in the mesoappendix.
-很明显实习医生的缝线断开了 -给我3号缝线
-Apparently the stitches the interns did came off.-Hand me another 3-0 silk.
-糟糕 我要将它尽量吸出来
Damn i need some more suction.
-她的血压多少 支持得住吗? -74心脏收缩
How's her pressure holding up? 74 systolic.
-她在出血 -我什么也看不见 -残余部分没有被正确得缝合
She is really bleeding.I can't see anything.The stump isn't closed right.
-她需要做盲肠部分切除术 -我找不到阑尾动脉
-She needs a partial cecectomy.-I can't get to the appendiceal artery.
你可以的 你就快找到了
Come on. Yes you can.You almost had it.
你的视觉好些了吗?
Is your visualization better?
-不 我还是 什么都看不见
-不要惊慌失措
这里 把它放下来
Here put that down.
跟着阑尾系膜摸下去
Feel down for the mesoappendix.
可以了 找脉动
All right Find the pulsations.
跟着它找到另一端
Now follow it to the end.
好像 我想我找到了
It feels...Okay i think i got it.
好的 这里 放入你的夹具
Good. Here place your clamp.
好的 对
Okay yeah. That's right.
好的 格蕾 你把它打结
Okay grey you tie it off
杨 在那个地方拿住夹具
While yang holds the clamp in place.
打结还是绷带缝合?
Stick tie or ligature suture?
只要有用就可以
Hey hey whatever works.
你们必须做你们觉得正确的事
You'll have to do what feels right to you.
绷带缝合
Ligature suture.
我们会去监狱吗?
Are we gonna go to jail?
你不会去监狱
You're not gonna go to jail
因为你还在手术室里
'Cause you didn't have the balls to stay in the room.
我们中剩下的会去监狱
The rest of us are gonna go to jail.
我刚刚听说了
I just heard.
到底怎么了?
What the hell happened?
我们住在一起 你应该找我帮你啊
We live together.You should've come to me.
那又能怎样 你 你可以救我
So what you...You could've saved me?
不 但可能我可以阻止你
No but maybe I could've stopped you.
不 这与你无关
No this isn't about you.
乔治 这是我做过的唯一一件
George this is the one thing That i have done
在过去的几个月里
In the past few months
与引起你对我的注意无关的事
That wasn't about getting you To notice me.
这是我做的 与你一点关系都没有
I did this. You had nothing to do with it.
整件事只与我有关
This was all me.
老兄
Dude.
她像是爱上你啦
She's like in love with you.
你怎么还木知木觉的？
How did you miss that?
紧急呼叫 我得走了
It's 9-1-1.I have to go.
好 那你走吧
Okay so go.
这是不是
Is this the part where...
你重返天堂的时刻 或者说
You go back to heaven Or wherever
是你跟你那些已经死去的朋友
And you And your dead guy friends
去聊聊这事有多好的时候
Talk about how great it was
聊聊你让我们共度最后一刻春宵的事
That you gave me This last night together
我靠回忆得到慰藉 然后继续生活
That i... Needed it To grieve and move on?
我和那些死去的朋友聊最多的是体育
Me and my dead guy friends Mostly talk about sports.
丹尼
Denny.
伊兹 去吧
Izzie go.
我哪里都不去
I'm not going anywhere.
准备好 可以开始了
We're just about ready.
亲爱的 对不起 我总有一大堆疯狂想法
I'm sorry honey For all my crazy.
不要说对不起
Don't be sorry.
我爱你 即使你总是疯言疯语
I love you even crazy.
那好 这些年来我一直忍受你的废话连篇
Okay i've taken Your crap all these years.
今天我的“废物”终于能派上用场了
It's finally time For you to take mine.
我来这里支持我妻子的
I'm here for my wife
但我觉得要想我们的性生活保持协调
But i think it's better for our Sex life
我还是不要看这些
if i don't see this
我会在大厅等她
So i'll be here for her Down in the lobby.
没刺了 我们清干净了整个突发区
No more spikes. We've Eliminated the seizure area.
他终于可以在晚上安心睡个好觉了
Now he can finally get A decent night's sleep.
他怎么会不知道他晚上会发作呢
How did he not know This was happening?
稍等 为什么连没有发现都是他的错
Wait why is it his fault For not noticing?
他活这么久都以为
He's going through his life Thinking that
他们之间的友谊就是她跟他说心事
they had The kind of relationship Where she could talk to him
她有事的时候会告诉他
If she was in trouble She would tell him.
如果你真的对某人有好感
If you really have feelings For someone
如果你真的爱他 你就跟他说 不是吗
If you really love them Then you talk to them right?
也许她尝试了
Maybe she tried.
我们不知道他们之间发生了什么
We don't know what went on Between them.
也许她不知道如何去表达
Maybe words failed her.
有时候
Sometimes...
词不达意
Words fail.
等你爸爸做完手术
Your dad Won't be out of surgery
至少要一个小时之后
For at least another hour.
你可以小睡一会儿
You could have a little nap.
什么 你才13岁
What you're 13
就喝咖啡
You're hitting The hard stuff?
我喜欢这味道
I like the taste.
把我养大的父母
I was raised by parents
并不想养小孩
Who weren't very interested In having kids.
他们有朋友 有自己的生活
They had friends.They had lives.
晚上他们很少在我身边
They weren't around much At night.
在我睡觉之前 我总是把所有电视都开了
And before i went to bed I'd turn on all the tvs...
房子里所有的灯 甚至是橱柜灯 也全开了
Every light in the house Even in the closets.
但我仍然睡不着
Still couldn't sleep.
有时想睡觉也很难啊
It's hard to sleep
在自家中也感到不安全时 就难以入睡 对吧
When you don't feel safe In your own house isn't it?
是啊
Yeah.
把咖啡给我
Give me that.
你现在要睡一会儿
You are going to sleep.
不
No.
我可不允许别人对我说不的
I'm not taking no For an answer.
闭上眼睛 我会在这里陪着你
Close your eyes. I'll be here.
来啊
Go on...
闭上眼睛
Close your eyes.
闭上你的眼睛
我刚才正在睡觉
I was sleeping
我能睡着可不容易啊
And sleep isn't easy For me to come by.
但当我终于能够睡个好觉时 手机响了
But i was finally sleeping Then i get a call--
我不敢相信 我仍然不能相信
I can't believe it. I still can't believe it.
不要为了此事 自己过不去
Don't beat yourself up Too much about it.
我看到你们俩成熟了很多
I've seen a lot of maturity In the two of you
在这次乱子中
Through this whole mess.
你们处理了危机 进行了手术
You handled the crisis You handled the surgery
你们救了那女孩的命
You saved that girl's life.
你们懂得马上求救
And you called for help Right away.
要是在不久之前
There was a time Not so long ago
你们不会这样做
That you would've reached A different conclusion.
你们会严守秘密 自己动手救那女孩
You could've stuck to the code And saved your own
拼命要掩盖整个乱子
Tried to hide the whole mess.
你要知道 有时保护同僚是团结的表现
You know sometimes protecting Your colleagues is solidarity.
但有时 只是傲慢的表现
And sometimes It's just hubris.
我很高兴你们懂得个中的差异
I'm glad to see You know the difference.
主任
Chief
我 我不能让你们俩因为这个招惹到麻烦
I-i can't let you two Get in trouble for this.
-莱西 -我做错了 他们尝试阻止我
-Lexie -No it's not right.People tried to stop me.
杨医生昨天叫我住手
Dr. Yang told me yesterday To shut it down
但我没有听她讲
But i didn't listen.
你昨天就知道了
You knew about this yesterday?
-主任 我 -你知道吗
-Sir I... -Did you know?
不知道
No.
你昨天就知道？你昨天就知道 -不
-You knew? You knew... -No!
-他们要把她切开 -不
-They were gonna cut her open? -No!
莱西刚才说你知道
Lexie just said you knew.
缝合线 我知道他们要在自己身上练习缝合线
Sutures. I knew they were Doing sutures on themselves
我觉得我没必要说出来
And i didn't think i needed To say anything
因为我已经让他们住手 我处理了
Because i had shut it down I had handled it.
很显然 你没有处理好
Apparently you didn't
因为莱西差点丢了工作
Because it almost Cost lexie her job
更不要提赛迪差点死在手术台了
Not to mention that sadie Almost died in there.
行 你知道吗 赛迪自己划开自己肚皮的
Okay you know what? Sadie did that to herself.
还有 别假装
And let's not pretend
你跟莱西好像有某种关系似的
That you have some sort Of relationship with lexie.
别假装说你关心她
Let's not pretend That you care about her.
我担心自己能否保住饭碗
I care about my job
我想做正确的事
And i care about doing The right thing.
你以为自己是谁 给我讲是非对错
Who are you to lecture me On doing the right thing?
你开玩笑啊 你不是主诊医生 梅丽迪斯
Are you kidding me? You're not An attending meredith.
也许你睡了主诊医生 但你不是主诊医生
You may be sleeping with one. But you aren't one yet.
我们是为了这事而争论吗 德瑞克
Is that what this Is about--derek?
总是要牵扯到德瑞克吗
It's always Gonna be about derek?
好 不说德瑞克 这是你与我之间的事
Okay fine it's not about Derek. It's about you and me
你刚才没有在房间里支持我
And the fact that you didn't Have my back in that room.
你想要我说些什么呢
What would you Have wanted me to say?
我不知道 什么都可以讲啊
I don't know. Anything.
除了不你什么都可以讲
You should've said anything.
你跟主任有关系
You have a relationship With the chief.
他听你的
You have his ear
但是你一句维护我的话都没有说
But you didn't say anything To defend me.
因为错的并不只有我
Because this isn't just on me.
我意思是 你就站在那
I mean you just stood there
他不让我做主刀手术 你也坐视不理
And you watched him take me out Of the running for solo surgery.
你让我独自承受责难
You let me take all the blame
但事实上 我们的实习生都在那房间里
But the fact is that we all Had interns in that room.
我们都没有尽好监督他们的责任
We all failed To supervise them.
如果你的朋友在手术台死去
And if your friend Had died in there
如果我们没有挽救她的性命
If you and i Hadn't saved her life
我们大家都有责任
That would've been On all of us too.
你应该说这些
You should've said that.
你干嘛看着我
Why are you looking at me?
我们在想 那些实习生
We were just wondering...The interns...
你要对他们说什么呢
What you're Going to say to them.
不不 我累了
D--unh-unh. No no. I'm tired.
我什么都不会对那些实习生说
I'm not saying anything To the interns.
我已经带大了我的小屁孩 你们就是我的小屁孩
I raised my babies. You were my babies.
现在 你们都长大了
Now you all grown folks.
责任在你们身上 自己的小屁孩自己带
It's on you. You raise your own babies.
我们一定得向他们训话
So we have to talk to 'em?
-你的小屁孩 -我们该说什么呢
-Your babies. -What do we say?
你们真的想要我长篇大论吗
Do you really need A speech from me
经历了这么多 此时此刻
At this point After all this time?
因为 如果你们真的想 你们不配在这
Because i mean if you do You shouldn't even be here.
如果你们真想 那我教育方式就错了
If you do then i haven't Raised you right
但我知道 我用正确的方式教育了你们
And i know I raised you right.
所以 我是不会给你们大发言论了
No you don't get A speech from me.
是时候自己想清楚该怎么教育下一代了
It's time for you To make your own speeches.
格雷医生 讲述病情
Dr. Grey present.
赛迪 哈里斯 30岁
Sadie harris 30
阑尾切除术后三小时
Three hours status Post-appendectomy
手术期间伴有大量出血
Complicated By severe hemorrhaging.
-死神 你们在干嘛 -斯波尔丁医生
-Death what is this? -Dr. Spalding.
体征稳定 加三倍抗生素
Vitals stable Triple antibiotic coverage.
两周内她能够完全康复
She should fully recover Within two weeks.
还有么
And?
还有 我们 也就是给你动手术的人
And...We your surgeons...
犯了错误 危害了你的健康
Made mistakes That compromised your care
这种错误 在这所医院并不多见
Mistakes that reflect poorly On this hospital
这种事不会再发生
And that won't happen again.
立即生效
Effective immediately
这里的所有实习生都会降为见习生
Every intern here Is on probation.
有任何轻举妄动 你们就完蛋了
So much as sneeze...And you're done.
你们每个人都禁止进去手术室
None of you will see The inside of an o.r.
除非接到进一步通知
Until further notice.
你们失去了主任对你们的尊重 相信我
You've lost the chief's respect Which believe me
要拿回来可不简单
Is not an easy thing To get back.
就我自己而言 我已经不再尊重你们了
And speaking for myself You've lost my respect
而且尊重很可能一去就不复返
And you probably won't ever Get that back.
但他仍然尊重伊兹斯蒂文斯
But he still Respects izzie stevens.
你说什么
What did you say?
你仍然尊重伊兹斯蒂文斯
You seem To still respect izzie stevens
但她杀了一个病人
And she killed a patient.
她尽力去挽救一个人的生命
She was trying To save a man's life.
你为了找乐子差点杀了一个朋友
And you almost killed A friend for fun.
这不一样
It's different.
你还好吧
How you doing?
在这里能够吃到好药
Oh... They give Good drugs here.
我是不是看上去很丑
Do i look bad?
你看上去很美
Oh you look beautiful.
满脸都是荣誉徽章
Just badge of honor All over your face.
天啊
Oh god.
我有没有听错
Did i hear correctly
那些实习生想动刀想疯了
That the um interns Went scalpel crazy?
对 你没听错
Yes you did.
疯狂
Oh crazy.
他们的疯狂程度 我不知道怎么说
I don't know That they were--crazy.
我还记得做实习生的心情
I can remember what it's like--Being an intern
就是喜欢医学
Just loving medicine
谈及手术就很兴奋
Being so excited By surgery
发疯地想做手术 我什么都会做
Wanting to operate so badly That i'd do anything...
我不停地长时间地跳来跳去
That i couldn't stop bouncing Up and down long enough
就为了能够拿到手术刀
To even hold a scalpel.
现在
Now...
现在怎样
Now?
我能做大部分的手术
i can do Most of my surgeries
根本不需要动脑筋
Without even Thinking about it.
就好像我在开车
It's like i'm driving.
不知不觉就到家了
Suddenly i'm at home
我甚至不知道怎么就到了
I don't even know How i got there.
一成不变
It's rote.
大多的手术我都不记得了
I don't even remember Most surgeries...
大部分我救过的人
Most of the lives i save.
住院医生呢 她们努力工作
And the residents They're working so hard
发疯般地工作 就为了做一次主刀手术
Just working like crazy To get to do a solo surgery
而我已经厌恶了这类手术
That i have come to hate.
我讨厌阑尾切除术
I hate appys.
仅仅是因为 这手术很无聊
Just--appys bore me.
我讨厌当阑尾发热时
I resent the appendix For bothering to get hot
还要把它拿出来
And needing to come out.
我厌恶器官 那真是
I resent an organ. That's...
我不知道
I don't know.
也许我一点都不想做普通外科手术
Maybe i don't want to do General surgery after all.
也许我需要一个新的挑战
Maybe i need A new challenge.
也许我需要一些令我兴奋到到处乱跳的东西
Maybe i need something To make me bounce up and down.
也许我已经累了
Maybe i'm just tired.
可以的
It's okay...
累了 是可以的
To be tired.
对吧
Right?
你也累了
You're tired too?
我筋疲力尽了
I'm exhausted.
心底深处 疲惫不堪
Deep-down-inside exhausted.
我只是 我想
I just--i want...
我不知道
I don't know.
但我想要一些东西
But i want something.
我们俩都这么想
Well that makes Two of us.
睡眠
Sleep...
是最容易的事
It's the easiest thing to do.
要做的
You just...
就是闭上眼睛
Close your eyes.
好 行 做手术是个坏主意
Okay fine. The surgery Was a bad idea.
不是坏 是糟透了
No it was A terrible idea.
作为你的上司 我要说的是
And speaking as your boss
这个主意鲁莽而且不负责任
It was an irresponsible And reckless idea
不禁让我认真思考
That makes me Seriously question
-你有没有做一个好医生的能耐 -死神
-If you have what it takes To be a good doctor. -death
作为你的朋友 我想问
And as your friend...
你究竟搞什么鬼啊
What the hell Is going on with you?
我不知道
I don't know.
但对我们大多数人来说
But for so many of us
睡眠并不是呼之即来的
Sleep seems out of our grasp.
谢谢
Thank you.
你妈妈过去看到我有多累
Your mom used to see How tired i was.
常常叫你把我带回家
She used to make you Bring me home
因为我总是孑然一身 需要家庭温暖
'Cause i was all alone And needed a family.
那是好事
That was a good thing.
所以 要么你带她回去 不然就我带
So either you bring her home Or i will.
我们心中有渴望
We want it
但是 我们不知道该如何获得
But... We don't know How to get it.
我不知道我为什么来到这里
I don't know Why i came here.
你想进去吗
Do you want to come in?
不不 我觉得那不合适
No. No. I-i don't think That'd be appropriate.
行 那你想去别的地方吗
Well do you want to go Some place else?
不
No.
我觉得你很漂亮
I think you're beautiful.
但是一旦我们勇于直面心中的恶魔
But once we face our demons...
面对恐惧
Face our fears...
-莱西在这里 -是啊
-Lexie's here. -Yeah.
-你在为她铺床吗 -是啊
-Are you making up A bed for her? -Yeah.
你把无家可归的人带回家了
You brought home a stray.
是啊
Yeah.
向人求救 互相帮助
And turn to each other For help...
我要抓紧时间补眠
I'm gonna try To grab some sleep.
六小时之后我又要回医院去了
I gotta be back At the hospital in six hours.
阿历克斯 等一下
Alex wait. Um...
我的生活一团糟
I'm a mess.
我冲动鲁莽 神经质 乱糟糟 我都知道
I'm a flat-out freaking mess. I know that.
我知道
I know and...
对不起 你值得比我好一百倍的人
I'm sorry. You deserve a lot better.
别再说了
Stop.
听好 如果你不想跟我在一起
Look if you don't want To be with me
现在对你来说喘不过气
If this is too much for you Right now
没问题
That's okay.
但如果你想跟我分手
But you're gonna have to Break up with me
因为我哪里都不会去
'Cause i'm not Going anywhere.
我能够处理乱子
I can handle the mess.
那么决定权在你那
So it's up to you.
你要进来不
You coming?
对不起
I'm sorry.
我不能
I can't...
没事
It's okay.
我就在这里
I'll be right here.
没事
It's okay.
黑夜其实并不是那么可怕 因为
Nighttime isn't So scary because...
我们发现 黑夜里我们并不是孤身一人
We realize we aren't all alone In the dark.